<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.estuary-sosac" version="3.0.0" name="Estuary-sosac" provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman">
	<requires>
		<trycatch>
            <try>
                <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.15.0"/>
            </try>

            <catch>
                <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.16.0"/>
            </catch>
        </trycatch>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/xbmc/skin.estuary/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">مظهر Estuary بواسطة phil65. ( مظهر كودي الافتراضي )</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Абалонка &quot;Estuary&quot; ад phil65. (прадвызначаная абалонка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary skin af phil65 (Kodis standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary Skin von phil65. (Kodi-Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary skin by phil65 and Piers. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary, creado por phil65 and Piers (skin por defecto de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Máscara Estuary por phil65 y Piers. (La máscara predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Estuary rüü autor on phil65. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Estuary azala phil65-ek egina. (Kodiren azal lehenetsia)</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوستهٔ اسچوری به دست phil65. (پوستهٔ پیش‌گزیدهٔ کودی)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary-ulkoasun ovat kehittäneet phil65 ja Piers. (Kodin oletusulkoasu)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d&apos;origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של קודי)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (Zadana Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Estuary oleh phil65. (Skin default Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Estuary-skinnið eftir phil65. (sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary di phil65. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuaryスキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65가 만든 Estuary 스킨. (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Estuary skin by phil65. (Kodi&apos;s default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi&apos;s standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa phil65. (domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary de phil65. (Temă implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary от phil65 (стандартная обложка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary, vytvorili phil65. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary, ett skal av phil65. (Kodi&apos;s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodnŏ skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi&apos;nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary від phil65 і Piers. (стандартна обкладинка Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Estuary của phil65. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 开发的 Estuary 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary-sosac je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 19.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary-sosac is the default skin for Kodi 19.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary-sosac is the default skin for Kodi 19.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary-sosac is the default skin for Kodi 19.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
	</extension>
</addon>
